没有  这是我到纽约第一次听音乐会
No, no. this is my first concert in new york.
你没跟我说过
You didn't tell me that.
得了吧你
Get the hell outta here.
在美国  用什么理由开夏令营都行
In america, they have summer camps for everything.
贵族营  篮球营  魔术营
Rich kids, basketball camp, magic camp.
-网球营  -对  还有导演营
- tennis camp. - tennis camp. movie director camp!
还该搞一个集中营
They should have a concentration camp.
两周强化训练成长
Two weeks mandatory for all kids growing up,
了解如何发挥人类的潜力
So they would finally understand what the human race is capable of.
太妙了  不过谁会送孩子去集中营
Brilliant! except who'd send their kid to a concentration camp?
有责任心的父母  希望孩子把握现实的
A responsible parent who wants their child to grasp reality.